https://akshay.com/privacypolicy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyAkshay Software2020-07-30T11:45:27+00:00
AKSHAY SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES LTD. - PRIVACY POLICY
When you submit your information or use our services, you trust us with your information. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. This is important; we hope you will take time to read it carefully.
‘Akshay Software Technologies Limited’ respects your privacy and it is very important to us. As per our policy, we may collect any information from you across our website https://www.akshay.com and other sites/pages we own and operate.
Many of our services require you to sign up for a product or service you are interested in. When you do so, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number etc.
We always collect the information with your knowledge and consent. We retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
